Guide to the Charles Gould Morris Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Daguerrotypes and Photographs, 1850-1915; Series III; 0.5; (1 box)
  - Daguerreotypes
    - [Higgins, Sarah?], undated (Box 48, Folder 261)
    - Morris, Eli James: "middling size, poorly shod, and reasonably old", undated (Box 48, Folder 261)
    - Morris, Luzon Burritt, undated (Box 48, Folder 262)
    - Morris; Luzon Burritt, undated (Box 48, Folder 262)
    - "Newcomb group: Sophie, George, Ellen, Edward, about 1850", Circa1850 (Box 48, Folder 263)
    - Tuttle, Lucius Bement, undated (Box 48, Folder 263)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 48, Folder 263)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 48, Folder 264-265)
  - Photographs
    - Appleton, Julius, undated (Box 48, Folder 266)
    - Appleton, Lena (Allen), 1870, undated (Box 48, Folder 266)
    - Ashly, William Lucius, and Roy David (Box 48, Folder 266)
    - Ashley: "Gertrude's children, our grandchildren," signed "Grace -- Lucius [Tuttle?], undated (Box 48, Folder 266)
    - Bassett, Fannie C.W., undated (Box 48, Folder 267)
    - Bradley, Edward E.: "Adj. Gen. of Conn.", 1895 (Box 48, Folder 267)
    - Morris, Eli James, with notes, undated (Box 48, Folder 267)
    - Morris, Eli James, and Jane E. Morris, undated (Box 48, Folder 267)
    - Morris, Jane E., undated (Box 48, Folder 267)
    - Morris, Luzon Burritt: "age about 50", undated (Box 48, Folder 268)
    - Morris, Lydia (Bennett), undated (Box 48, Folder 268)
    - Morris, Martha Jane, 1866 (Box 48, Folder 268)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 48, Folder 268)
    - Houses in Madison and Newtown, Connecticut, Circa1900-1915 (Box 48, Folder 268)
      See also: box 7, folders 38-39 box 37, folder 199 box 39, folder 215-216 box 40, folder 218 box 46, folder 256-261
- Additional Material, 1948-1959, undated; Accession 1992-M-022; 0.25; (1 box)
  Received from: Helen Forbes (Mrs. Thomas), 1991 Oct 4
  Addition inventory by Carol King 1992 Jan
  This addition was the gift of Mrs. Helen Forbes, widow of Professor Thomas R. Forbes of the Yale Medical School. The material belonged to Professor Forbes's father, James Bruff Forbes.
  - Correspondence, 1948-1959, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Speeches, notes, [1948?], 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photograph, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)